Guide to the Radio TV Services Records, circa 1937-2012 UA.27.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Sound Recordings, 1960-1988 and undated
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes, 1960-1975; undated; 4.2
    - Memorial Service at Duke Chapel for Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., Apr. 6, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0190)
      Original identification number: B-643-B
    - Memorial Service at Duke Chapel for Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., Apr. 6, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0191)
      Original identification number: B-643-C
    - Statement by Mr. Wright Tisdale to students in Silent Vigil, Apr. 10, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0192)
      Original identification number: B-644
    - North Carolina News Conference featuring Miss Bunny Small on the Silent Vigil, Apr. 22, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0193)
      Original identification number: B-645
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. John Vernberg on A Barrier in the Sea, Mar. 6, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0194)
      Original identification number: B-646-A
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. John Vernberg on the I.B.P. Program, Mar. 6, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0195)
      Original identification number: B-646-B
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. Ralph Brauer on his experiments at the lab, Mar. 6, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0196)
      Original identification number: B-647-A
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. Ralph Brauer on Hydra I, Mar. 6, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0197)
      Original identification number: B-647-B
    - Oceanography: News Conference with Dr. Ralph Brauer on Hydra I, May 3, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0198)
      Original identification number: B-648
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Mr. Ramsey Clark, U.S. Attorney General, May 8, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0199)
      Original identification number: B-649
    - Duke Homestead Ceremonies, Apr. 28, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0200)
      Original identification number: B-650
    - Dedication of the Duke Phytotron, May 10, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0201)
      Original identification number: B-651
    - Wallace Wade Day Dinner honoring Coach Wade, Great Hall, Sept. 1967 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0202)
      Original identification number: B-652-A
    - Wallace Wade Day Dinner honoring Coach Wade, Great Hall, Sept. 1967 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0203)
      Original identification number: B-652-B
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0204)
      Original identification number: B-653-A
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0205)
      Original identification number: B-653-B
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0206)
      Original identification number: B-653-C
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0207)
      Original identification number: B-653-D
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0208)
      Original identification number: B-653-E
    - Interview with Mrs. Mildred Hendrix on the Duke Chapel organ, Jan. 1968; 0:31:31 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0209, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0011, Audio-file UA27020001-RR-0209_0001.wav)
      Original identification number: B-654-A
    - Interview with Mrs. Mildred Hendrix on the Duke Chapel organ, Jan. 1968; 0:23:12 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0210, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0012, Audio-file UA27020001-RR-0210_0001.wav)
      Original identification number: B-654-B
    - Duke University Organ recital, June 3, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0211)
      Original identification number: B-655
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Rev. Malcolm Boyd, Feb. 12, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0212)
      Original identification number: B-656-A
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Rev. Malcolm Boyd, Feb. 12, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0213)
      Original identification number: B-656-B
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Rev. Malcolm Boyd, Feb. 12, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0214)
      Original identification number: B-656-C
    - Baccalaureate Service Duke Chapel, June 2, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0215)
      Original identification number: B-657
    - Commencement Exercises: Dr. Barnes Woodhall, June 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0216)
      Original identification number: B-658
    - Joint News Conference: Dr. Albert Whiting, Pres N.C. College, and Dr. R. Taylor Cole, Provost Duke University, July 17, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0217)
      Original identification number: B-659
    - Discussion about the Duke Chapel organ, July 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0218)
      Original identification number: B-660
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Ambassador George C. McGhee, Sept. 24, 1968 (Box 9, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0219)
      Original identification number: B-661-A
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Ambassador George C. McGhee, Sept. 24, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0220)
      Original identification number: B-661-B
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Ambassador George C. McGhee, Sept. 24, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0221)
      Original identification number: B-661-C
    - News Conference with Mr. James Gardner held at Duke University Law School, Apr. 29, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0222)
      Original identification number: B-662
    - Dr. Clark Kerr's address in Page Aud., Nov. 18, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0223)
      Original identification number: B-664
    - Student Activism: Interview with 3 students about Silent Vigil at Duke, Apr. 10, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0224)
      Original identification number: B-665
    - Student Activism: Mr. Clarence Whitefield's address to Kiwanis Club on student unrest, Mar. 3, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0225)
      Original identification number: B-666-A
    - Student Activism: Mr. Clarence Whitefield's address to Kiwanis Club on student unrest, Mar. 3, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0226)
      Original identification number: B-666-B
    - Student Activism: Alan Kerckhoff speaking in Page Auditorium on student unrest, Feb. 16, 1969; 0:31:33 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0227, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0013, Audio-file UA27020001-RR-0227.wav)
      Original identification number: B-667-A
    - Student Activism: Alan Kerckhoff speaking in Page Auditorium on student unrest, Feb. 16, 1969; 0:17:37 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0228, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0014, Audio-file UA27020001-RR-0228.wav)
      Original identification number: B-667-B
    - Student Activism: Comments at Univ. House by Dr. Knight and members of student body, Feb. 15, 1969; 0:43:17 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0229, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0015, Audio-file UA27020001-RR-0229.wav)
      Original identification number: B-668
    - Student Activism: Dr. Douglas Knight's appearance on N.C. News Conf., Oct. 14, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0230)
      Original identification number: B-669
    - Student Activism: Development Dinner-Raleigh, N.C. Q&A portion-Mr. Charles B. Wade, Apr. 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0231)
      Original identification number: B-670
    - Convocation: Dr. Douglas Knight, Sept. 18, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0232)
      Original identification number: B-673-A
    - Mr. Michael Harrington speaking in Page Aud., Oct. 15, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0233)
      Original identification number: B-674-A
    - Mr. Michael Harrington speaking in Page Aud., Oct. 15, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0234)
      Original identification number: B-674-B
    - Mr. Michael Harrington speaking in Page Aud., Oct. 15, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0235)
      Original identification number: B-674-C
    - Dr. Knight: Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 7, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0236)
      Original identification number: B-676-A
    - Dr. Knight: Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 7, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0237)
      Original identification number: B-676-B
    - Dr. Knight: Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 7, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0238)
      Original identification number: B-676-C
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's address to Academic Council Meeting, Dec. 19, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0239)
      Original identification number: B-677-A
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's address to Academic Council Meeting, Dec. 19, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0240)
      Original identification number: B-677-B
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's address to Executive Committee-Trustee Meeting, Dec. 7, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0241)
      Original identification number: B-681-A
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's address to Executive Committee-Trustee Meeting, Dec. 7, 1968 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0242)
      Original identification number: B-681-B
    - Board of Trustees: Reports from Dean Pye, Dr. Knight, Mr. Huestis, Mar. 28, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0243)
      Original identification number: B-683
    - Commencement: Hon. Angier Biddle Duke's Address, June 2, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0244)
      Original identification number: B-684-A
    - Commencement: Hon. Angier Biddle Duke's Address, June 2, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0245)
      Original identification number: B-684-B
    - Baccalaureate: Dr. Knight delivers final sermon, June 1, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0246)
      Original identification number: B-685
    - The Office of President: Interview with Dr. Knight, Apr. 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0247)
      Original identification number: B-686-A
    - The Office of President: Interview with Dr. Knight, Apr. 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0248)
      Original identification number: B-686-B
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 31, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0249)
      Original identification number: B-687-A
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 31, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0250)
      Original identification number: B-687-B
    - Convocation: Dr. Woodhall and Dr. Hobbs, Sept. 25, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0251)
      Original identification number: B-688
    - Mr. Howard Fuller: Speech at beginning of Black Week, Feb. 15, 1970 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0252)
      Original identification number: B-702
    - Impression of Campus unrest by Mr. Charles Braswell, 1969 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0253)
      Original identification number: B-705
    - President Sanford: Strike Day Activities, May 6, 1970 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0254)
      Original identification number: B-709
    - President Sanford: Duke Blue Devil Club Breakfast, Aug. 4, 1970 (Box 10, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0255)
      Original identification number: B-710
    - Terry Sanford: N.C. News Conference, Sept. 14, 1970 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0256)
      Original identification number: B-711
    - Terry Sanford: Inauguration Ceremonies, Oct. 18, 1970 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0257)
      Original identification number: B-712
    - Major Speakers Series: Senator George McGovern, Oct. 18, 1970 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0258)
      Original identification number: B-713
    - Terry Sanford speaks to the Rotary and Tobaccoland Kiwanis Club, May 18, 1970 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0259)
      Original identification number: B-714
    - A. Kenneth Pye talks to the Tobaccoland Kiwanis Club on Law Day, 1970 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0260)
      Original identification number: B-715
    - News Conference: Introducing Mike McGee as new Duke football coach, undated (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0261)
      Original identification number: B-716
    - Alumni Lecture Series: Duke in the 70's, undated (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0262)
      Original identification number: B-722
    - Dedication of the A. Hollis Edens Residence Halls, May 2, 1970 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0263)
      Original identification number: B-723
    - Protestant Hour: Duke Chapel Choir, May 23, 1971 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0264)
      Original identification number: B-724
    - Protestant Hour: Duke Chapel Choir, June 6, 1971 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0265)
      Original identification number: B-725
    - Protestant Hour: Duke Chapel Choir, June 20, 1971 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0266)
      Original identification number: B-726
    - Presentation Ceremony: Codex Vaticanus to Rare Book Room Perkins Library, Sept. 24, 1971 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0267)
      Original identification number: B-727
    - Eddie Cameron comments on Old Football Film of Duke games: Talk to Durham Kiwanis Club, undated (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0268)
      Original identification number: B-728
    - Testimonial Dinner for Dean Robert E. Cushman, May 24, 1971 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0269)
      Original identification number: B-729
    - Retirement Dinner for Eddie Cameron, 1972 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0270)
      Original identification number: B-730
    - Retirement Dinner for Dr. Joseph Spengler, Prof. of Economics, 1972 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0271)
      Original identification number: B-731
    - Commencement, 1972 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0272)
      Original identification number: B-732
    - Commencement, 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0273)
      Original identification number: B-735
    - Major Speakers Series: Ms. Gloria Steinem and Dr. Greshem, Spring 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0274)
      Original identification number: B-736
    - Sanford meets with Triangle Mayors to offer Duke resources, Sept. 19, 1972 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0275)
      Original identification number: B-737
    - Founder's Day Service in Chapel with Sanford, undated (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0276)
      Original identification number: B-738
    - Mitch Mitchell talks about history of southern tenant farmers and general labor and farm problems, undated (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0277)
      Original identification number: B-739
    - Dr. H. Shelton Smith talks about the church's role in the development of racism, Jan. 10, 1970 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0278)
      Original identification number: B-740
    - Ms. Betty Friedan presents a Major Speakers lecture, Jan. 26, 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0279)
      Original identification number: B-741-A
    - Ms. Betty Friedan presents a Major Speakers lecture, Jan. 26, 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0280)
      Original identification number: B-741-B
    - B. F. Skinner presents a Major Speakers lecture, Fall 1972 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0281)
      Original identification number: B-742-A
    - B. F. Skinner presents a Major Speakers lecture, Fall 1972 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0282)
      Original identification number: B-742-B
    - Sen. Sam Ervin speaks to the Duke Law Forum, Spring 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0283)
      Original identification number: B-745
    - N.C. Sen Sam Ervin talks to N.C. Press-Duke Dinner, Jan. 1973; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0284)
    - Epoch Campaign Announcement: Sanford, Jones, McMahon, Fall 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0285)
      Original identification number: B-746
    - Terry Sanford's first news conference as Duke President, undated (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0286)
      Original identification number: B-747
    - Sanford announces candidacy for U.S. president, Spring 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0287)
      Original identification number: B-748
    - Alex Haley, Spring 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0288)
      Original identification number: B-749
    - Alex Haley, Spring 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0289)
      Original identification number: B-750
    - Impeachment rally on main quad, Fall 1973 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0290)
      Original identification number: B-751
    - Press Association Annual Meeting, Jan. 1974 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0291)
      Original identification number: B-752
    - Open Forum on student and campus related topics, Spring 1967 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0292)
      Original identification number: B-754
    - Open Forum on student and campus related topics, Spring 1967 (Box 11, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0293)
      Original identification number: B-755
    - Duke Major Speakers: Sander Vanocur, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0111)
      Original identification number: B-756
    - Stewart Udall predicts about energy crisis, Fall 1973 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0112)
      Original identification number: B-757
    - Tom Wolfe, author, speaks on youth, Fall 1973 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0113)
      Original identification number: B-758
    - Interview with Dr. Frank Slaughter, author, Fall 1973 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0114)
      Original identification number: B-759
    - Duke Major Speakers: Buckminster Fuller, Fall 1973 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0115)
      Original identification number: B-760
    - Duke Major Speakers: Buckminster Fuller, Fall 1973 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0116)
      Original identification number: B-761
    - Sanford's Inauguration as Duke President, undated, 1970 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0117)
      Original identification number: B-763
    - Dan Rather's speech at Duke University, 1974 January (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0118)
      Original identification number: B-764
    - Press conference held to announce the finding of the Monitor by Duke University and other researchers, 1974 March 07 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0119)
      Original identification number: B-765-A
    - Press conference held to announce the finding of the Monitor by Duke University and other researchers, 1974 March 07 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0120)
      Original identification number: B-765-B
    - Interview with John Newton, discoverer of the ship, the Monitor, 1974 March (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0121)
      Original identification number: B-766
    - News conference with John Newton and others, conducted on board press boat at sea, undated (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0122)
      Original identification number: B-767
    - Commencement: Trudeau, Robinson, Martin, 1974 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0123)
      Original identification number: B-768
    - Cesar Chavez speaking at Duke, 1974 September 11; 1:09:11 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0124, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0010, Audio-file UA27020001-RR-0124_01.wav, Audio-file UA27020001-RR-0124_02.wav)
      Original identification number: B-770
    - Durham Forum, 1974 October 20 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0125)
      Original identification number: B-771
    - Clarence Kelly, FBI Director, speaking at Duke, 1974 December 04 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0126)
      Original identification number: B-772
    - Milton Friedman speaking at Duke, 1975 January 24 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0127)
      Original identification number: B-773
    - Student World Day of Prayer, Vietnam Era, Bill Patton, undated (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0128)
    - Monitor: Interview with John Newton, 1974 March 07 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0129)
    - Study-in, DUB, 1963 March 01 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0130)
    - Dr. Hart, Dr. Knight: Speeches to Board of Trustees, 1967 November 13 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0131)
    - Wild Track: James B. Duke Prof. teaching class, scene 32B, undated (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0132)
    - Founder's Day Dinner: Knight, Tisdale, and Perkins, 1964 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0133)
    - King #1, undated (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0134)
    - King #2, undated (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0135)
    - Duke 140 Narration, Founder's Day, undated (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0136)
    - Ceremony to name the Duke Univ. Library the William R. Perkins Library, 1966 December 11 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0137)
    - The Duke Story, 1965 June 26 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0138)
    - The Duke Story: Interview-Dr. Knight in his office, undated (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0139)
    - Founder's Day: Christine Mims, 1972 December 03 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0140)
    - Founder's Day, circa 1962 (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0141)
    - Founder's Day: LaPrade, History of Duke, undated (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0142)
    - Ashmore explaining Vigil to staff, undated; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0143)
    - Study-in, 1967 November 13; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0144)
    - Knight and Cockschutt, 1969 June 4; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0145)
    - Introduction of Guest Speaker by Dr. Bisell, Address by Dr. Knight, President Duke Univ., Scarborough College, Toronto, 1966 October 04; 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0146)
    - Betty Friedan, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 12, Audio-reel UA27020001-RR-0147)
- Film and Video, circa 1937-1987 and undated
  Original recordings are closed to use. Digitized copies are available for some recordings. Please contact University Archives staff for more information.
  - Film, 1936-1979
    - Ace Parker 105 yd run & 70 yd return, 1936
      1 film reel (47 secs.): si., b&w; 3 inch.
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0107)
    - Year at Duke, 1937-1938; 16mm, black-and-white and color, silent; 0:08:07
      1 film reel (400 ft.): b&w; 7 inch.; From Description of Films: Duke University Women hold field day: Archery, Tennis, Softball, Horseback Riding, Steeple Chase; Carnation and Pageant -COLOR:; Ceres & Prosperine is given for entertainment for Queen and her court; May Day Exercises long; Centennial Commencement; Representatives from 46 orphanages homes through the Carolinas aided by the Duke Endowment pace a wreath on the James B. Duke tomb in the Duke Memorial Chapel; Picture of wreath and two kids and a man; Candidates for degrees and their parents are honored at a reception; President Few and some other gentleman standing there; Some kind of reception out in the open; Academic procession marching into chapel; Alumni hold annual luncheon; Dr. Few and others receiving honorary degrees (left to right): Dr. W. P. Few, Dr. Norman Vincent Peale, Rev. J. B. Craven, Gov. Clyde R. Hoey, Dr. Lewis Hill Weed, Dr. Charles Holmes Herty; Procession going out into football stadium; Flag is lowered as final act of school year; Someone going up stands to get to the flag; Numbered: 45
      - Original 16mm motion picture film (Box 16, Film-reel UA27020001-F16-0104)
      - Digital video preservation file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0057, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0104.mkv)
      - Digital video access file (Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0057, Video-file UA27020001-F16-0104.mp4)
    - Year at Duke leftover, 1937-1938